excellentanalytics.com 2015-06-08

# Outfox | Privacy Policy

**Cookies & web beacons**

To enhance your online experience, we use “cookies” or similar technologies. Cookies are text files placed in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. We do not track PII (personally identifiable information) using cookies. Any PII that is being handled must be actively submitted by you, it won’t be used to track your behavior, and it won’t be shared with third parties.

We use cookies to understand site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the content on our site.

We, or our third party service providers, may also use “web beacons” or clear .gifs, or similar technologies, which are small pieces of code placed on a web page, to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing web pages on our website.

In your browser, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience. Please consult the Help section of your browser for more information.

**Collection of information**

Some of our web pages may contain links to, or integrations with, other sites such as Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn, whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We also use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, and site analytics. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. We, our third party service providers, and/or partners may also place web beacons for these third parties. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement.

**International transfer**

We operate globally, so it is necessary to transfer your information internationally. In particular, your information will likely be transferred to and processed in the United States or Sweden, where our servers are. The data protection and other laws of other countries may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using this site, you consent to your information being collected, used, and transferred as set forth in this privacy statement.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to improve the user experience. If you do not wish to be tracked by Google Analytics on this, and other, website(s), then you can [download and install a browser add-on](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Please note that we do not, however, store any PII in Google Analytics.

Läs mer om cookies och integritet på svenska.
